<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<CHARACTERS>
	<CHARACTER id = "0">
		<NAME>Slaye</NAME>
		<IMAGE>slayeicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human</RACE>
		<GENDER>Female</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Mind Control</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Slaye is a super human hybrid. Her father crossed over in 1988 and married her mother in 1992. Slaye was then born in 1994. Her father mysteriously disappeared in 2002. She ran away from home in 2007.Growing up in the city alone Slaye has been able to develop her mind control powers extensively. She’s learnt to stay safe you needs to keep hidden and has used the people around her to get what she wants for years.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>MindControl</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "1">
		<NAME>[NAME 2]</NAME>
		<IMAGE>jbicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human?</RACE>
		<GENDER>Male</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Time Control</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>[NAME 2] has the ability to manipulate time but not travel through it. Little is known about [NAME 2]’s past, only that he suffered a great loss. It’s unknown what or who the great loss was, or why he wasn’t able to stop it. Since that day [NAME 2] has searched for ways to increase his powers of time control to allow travel through time and not just the control of it.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>TimeControl</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "2">
		<NAME>Turtle Man</NAME>
		<IMAGE>turtlemanicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human</RACE>
		<GENDER>Male</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Blockades</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>After years of working with machines (he) sees on the TV the influx of Super heroes that seem to be popping up, (he) decides that he could become one with all of his work with machines. Being slightly mad also helped. So he got to work seeing something many heroes lacked (he) created a way of producing walls from the very ground. The Nano bots that he had created helping him. Now working together with the other heroes he can help them by stopping the bad guys in their tracks or even funnelling them into areas to allow for special heroes to vanquish them.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>Blockades</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "3">
		<NAME>Doobies</NAME>
		<IMAGE>doobiesicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Alien</RACE>
		<GENDER>Male</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Telekenesis</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Centuries had past since (Doobies) had last awoken but then his ship suddenly awoke him he was orbiting earth. Believing this to be a safe haven he instructs his ship to enter the atmosphere and landed. (Doobies) race had the ability of telekinesis. Picking up object and moving them even flinging them if needed. It was these powers and of the monitoring of the global communications that he got in contact with the hero team and joined up to make this planet the safe haven he had hoped it was.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>Telekenesis</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "4">
		<NAME>Sgt Soldier Shooty (W.I.P)</NAME>
		<IMAGE>sgticon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human</RACE>
		<GENDER>Male</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Super Strength</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Sgt Soldier Shooty is a member of the UNITED STATES MARINE CORPS OOOOOHHHRAHHHHH! Or at least he was, after receiving a dishonourable discharge for firing three flares into the air to impress the base nurse on thanksgiving weekend and setting fire to his commanding officers soft top Corvette he got wind of a new cloning process, and because of his own self loving confidence he decided he wanted a copy of himself and all his masculine glory. But during his visit to the groups facility he overheard a conversation about their plans for a new world order and decided that is exactly his purpose in life, along with his desire to take down the government he served so… valiantly and that took a steaming dump of ungrateful disrespect on his chest. He was the perfect specimen for the group, they just had to take out the stupid and hype up the hatred in his clones, they also made them able to build muscle to the point even steroids wouldn’t be able to manage. And so the strongest man (or men, who knows how many they created) that ever lived was created.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>SuperStrength</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "5">
		<NAME>Evangeline Jacobs</NAME>
		<IMAGE>eveicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human</RACE>
		<GENDER>Female</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Wind</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Eve had a childhood fraught with abuse. Her grades were never good enough for her parents, her hair never pretty enough for her crush and her thoughts never important enough to express. She spent years in the shadow of her peers, being told at every turn that she just was not good enough for them, until one day Eve decided no more. Looking for a new start in life she came across the groups cloning, she wanted a version of herself that was thoughtful, strong and pretty but the group didn’t see her as a viable candidate for the cloning process. As another rejection was thrown in her face for the first time in her life Eve got mad, she burst into the groups headquarters and let go the most ear piercing, glass shattering scream that just seemed to go on forever. This is when the group realised her talent, what they could use her for… with a lung capacity like that, with a little bit of tweaking she could create a wall of air stronger than a hurricane.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>Wind</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "6">
		<NAME>Character 1(Alien Descendant)</NAME>
		<IMAGE>squidicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human Alien Hybrid</RACE>
		<GENDER>Female Squid</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Flame Thrower</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Born in the London suburbs [Insert Character Name] was immediately a little odd. As far as her parents were concerned it was just normal for a growing child until she reached the age of 9 and her powers became far more apparent and she was seamlessly able to wield the abilities of fire. She was powers became far more apparent and she was seamlessly able to wield the abilities of fire. She was able to hide it from her parents and the general public for 7 long years until that day.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>Fire</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "7">
		<NAME>Sidj</NAME>
		<IMAGE>bjicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Alien</RACE>
		<GENDER>Male</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Electricity</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Nobody knows from whence he came or how long he has lived. Some say he is from the [Insert alien invader planet] others say he is an immortal who was the first to receive powers from his god to defeat the invaders. All that is known is that he appears and disappears just as quick again. The side in which he chooses to fight is completely up to him. This could be from helping the British invade India to then be fighting on the side of the Nazis in World War 2. </DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>Lightning</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "8">
		<NAME>Jessie “Tsunami” Klein</NAME>
		<IMAGE>jessieicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human</RACE>
		<GENDER>Female</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Tsunami</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Nina has lost her human form. She is composed entirely of Amethyst water. Using her power, Nina is able to access any location by slipping through the cracks in the infrastructure. Due to this nature, Nina is a key component of any major heist. However cool she may be, she certainly is reckless. During a recent bar fight at sleeze-pit in Adelaide, Nina brought down her force on her fellow fighter so bad that the resulting tsunami caused the state of South Australia to separate from the mainland to become its own island.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>Tsunami</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
	<CHARACTER id = "9">
		<NAME>Terry “The Baron” Kershaw</NAME>
		<IMAGE>baronicon</IMAGE>
		<RACE>Human</RACE>
		<GENDER>Male</GENDER>
		<ABILITY>Oil</ABILITY>
		<DESCRIPTION>Terry is the… let’s say the special one at Amethyst. For what he lacks in intelligence, he makes up in brawn. The Baron hit it rich in the crude oil business with his ability to generate oil, The Baron was able to supply those countries under sanction by the UN. During the Great New Zealand incident, The Baron supplied the stricken New Zealand rebels with cheap crude oil causing him to become Australia’s most wanted man and New Zealand to retain independence from Australia.</DESCRIPTION>
    <ABILITYCLASS>Oil</ABILITYCLASS>
  </CHARACTER>
</CHARACTERS>